

Wendel Amante

Graphic Designer

+63 9777 669 410 📞

wendellreyel@gmail.com

96 Mamatitang Mabalacat, Pampanga

https://wendelamante.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

Creative Freelance Web and Graphic Designer with 2 years of experience in developing engaging digital graphics for clients in broad range of industries. Well- trained at visual strategy, layout development, branding, and new media advertising. Demonstrated success working in collaborative environment, manifest leadership to conceptualize and execute effective marketing collateral.

Technical Skills

- Graphic Design
- Photography
- UX/ UIDesign
- Videography
- Front- end dev
- Microsoft Office
- Adobe Photoshop
- Programming
- Animation
- Canva

Achievements

■ Dean's Lister

Cavite State University
S.Y 2020- 2021 & 2021-2022

With Honors

University of Perpetual Help System- DALTA 2018

Certifications

- SMART Android Mobile App Development
 TESDA Online Program | 2022
- SMART Technopreneurship 101

TESDA Online Program | 2022

Fortinet's Network Security Expert
Certification NSE 1 and NSE 2 Network
Security Associate

Fortinet | 2020

▼ TESDA 2D Animation NC II Genesis Innovations and Creative Design Training Center Inc. | 2018

Education

BS Information Technology

Cavite State University Imus- Campus 2018 - 2022

Information Communication Technology

University of Perpetual Help System- DALTA 2017 - 2019

Experiences

Aug 2021- Present

Freelance Graphic Designer

- Created mockups, logo, banners, and posters.
- Make PowerPoint Presentations and documentations.
- Contributed to front- end web design in Wordpress, Wix, Magento, and Shopify.
- Feb 2022- May 2022

Web Developer & Graphic Designer Intern

Inner SPARC Realty Services | Bacoor, Cavite

- Created graphic designs for marketing initiatives.
- Utilized WordPress in developing website.
- June 2020- June 2021

Lead Graphic Designer/ Content Creator/ Co- Web Designer and Developer

Street Mavens Clothing Company | Imus, Cavite

- Designed logo and produced graphic designs for streetwear clothing brand.
- Maintained a consistent social media feed through content creation.
- Developed and designed e-commerce website.

Projects

Street Mavens Clothing Company Website

• Php, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, MySQL

WTL Construction Inventory System

• JavaScript, Codelgniter, Bootstrap, Php, MySQL